How did people manage to survive in the past
?  Okay, an hour later
we'll take a look at the shoes.  And
quite honestly, I only
bought it because the price was right, and it
was even cheaper than at Action.  They were available there for
a while, too.  So, the
inside of the shoe, yes, is so dry
that it hardly
shows anything anymore.  So, if anything, 5%.
The question is, how does it feel?  There's
nothing better than stepping into warm shoes
.  The MOV is significantly
reduced.  It must be said quite clearly that
if you do that from the beginning, it wo
n't even arise in the first place.  But for just a
few bucks, I think it's a cool
idea, and it certainly wo
n't win any design awards, but
it doesn't have to dry like shoes anymore.
So, that's all for now.